

## CONTACT

706-512-5489

Atlanta, GA

celiardiller@gmail.com

in <u>LinkedIn</u>

<u>Portfolio</u>

#### EDUCATION

Certificate in UI Design-Specialization in Frontend Development for Designers

Career Foundry

March 2021 – December 2021

## BS in Biology and Business

St. Lawrence University

August 2016 – May 2020

#### SKILLS

- Adobe XS
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Photoshop
- Procreate
- Figma
- Marvel
- Atom
- Github

# CELIA DILLER

UI DESIGNER

#### SUMMARY

UX/UI Designer with a background in Biology and Business. Enjoys solving design problems and utilizing research findings to develop applications that are user friendly. Excelling in building low, mid, and high-fidelity wireframes with user testing and research

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Social Media Marketing Intern and Fundraising Consultant

The Desoto Theatre

Rome, GA

September 2020 – December 2021

- Increased over \$25,000 of donations and funding by creating digital content (Instagram posts/stories, Facebook posts, videos, and slideshows).
- Created marketing strategies for the Board to use that boosted ticket sales by 75% for various events.
- Created over a dozen digital presentations on marketing strategies which were performed to Board members to increase donations and ticket sales.
- Developed organizational system that preserved important historical documents and records that allow executives/board members to efficiently access the points needed to drive donor engagements and revenue.

## UI Designer and Business Developmental Intern

Sunflour Bakery

Rome, GA

June 2019 - February 2022

- Undertook a two-month long project as a UI Designer to design, photograph and code Sunflour Bakery's homepage and online ordering system on their website. Responsible for user testing, establishing brand direction, and visual components to increase marketing and sales for the company.
- Excelled at creating marketing strategies. Constructed a deep analysis with community feedback to create a better product for users.
- Created digital content to exemplify new products created. Resulted in sales increasing by 50%.
- Mastered the point-of-sale system (Clover) by handling set up of the system, maintaining online orders, adding/editing inventory, adding new employees and editing rewards systems for consumers. Resulted in a great customer satisfaction rate.

#### Sales Associate and Barista

Brewer Bookstore

Canton, NY

August 2016 – March 2020

- Created new product ideas, organizational optimization, and analytical skills to the team to increase sale revenue.
- Accomplished new and different requests to enhance customer experience and brand direction for the bookstore.
- Developed and implemented new training programs for new student workers in the café.

## SPECIALTIES

- Interface Design
- User Interviews, Testing and Personas
- Coding in HTML, Java-Script, and CSS
- Creating Brand Identities

- User Personas, Stories and Flows
- Typography and Iconography
- Mockups and Prototypes
- Social Media Marketing